Moore, David G. Additional Papers 5842
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
David G. Moore Additional Papers
1960-1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Moore, David G.
5842
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
5713643
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 12, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5681: New York State Governor's Committee on the State Employees' Retirement System Papers
Moore, David G. (David Gilbert), 1951-
5713643
- Interviews and notes from Study of Entrepreneurs which resulted in "The Enterprising Man" (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Speeches by Moore (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Other research documents (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Mobile Home Study (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Whirlpool (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Some ILR School-related folders (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Responsibilities of Committee Appointed to Study NY State Retirement System, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Meeting Notes, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  3/1
- Preliminary Report: "Pension Plans of Selected Private Companies in NY State", 1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Retirement Plan Benefit Tables, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Meeting Notes, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  8/26
- Retirement Plan Overviews, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Collective Bargaining, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Disability, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Comparative Data, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Relevant Laws, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Death Benefit (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Considerations, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- N.E.C., 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Options (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Service Benefit, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Advisory Commission, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Supplementation (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Transition and Variable Annuities (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Committee Action, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Study by Segal (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Teachers' Retirement, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Pamphlets, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Consultant's Report, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Minutes, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Minutes, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Fan Mail, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 27)